Hello everybody, welcome back to the
podcast. For today's guest, we have John
Kiriakou. Welcome in.
For today's co-host, we have Mike.
Welcome in, Mike.
So, please introduce yourself. In case
anybody doesn't know you and all that
one. Sure. I'm John Kiriakou, former CIA
counterterrorism officer, former chief
investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee, and uh convicted
criminal.
Convicted criminal? Can you go into that
>> Sure. I uh I was convicted of violating
the Intelligence Identities Protection
Act of 1982
after I blew the whistle on the CIA's
torture program. They came down on me
like a ton of bricks. I was utterly
unapologetic. Didn't anybody ever teach
you that snitches get stitches? Well,
that was the thing is that I had to be
the one given the stitches when I got
there.
>> Why is that? I thought you were
torturing people. No, I was the good
guy.
I didn't torture anybody.
But the terrorists did need to be
tortured.
Uh you know, sometimes you have to look
past that kind of thing. What? Why?
Cuz we got to be the good guys.
Right? We got to be a country of laws.
We have to be the good We're supposed to
be the shining But what if we make a law
that allows it? Allows to torture them.
That's different. If you want to torture
people,
I'm going to disagree with you, but you
got to change the law and then So,
you're against the idea of torturing
people.
>> idea of torturing. What if it's like a
loud dog?
Well,
I did try to kill a chicken one time cuz
it wouldn't stop crowing early in the
morning. Yeah, I mean, but a chicken is
food. A dog is domesticated, but it
still upsets me sometimes. And it's the
neighbor's dog, and I tried to feed the
dog poison, but it did nothing to him.
Oh, yeah. No, that's that's that's too
much.
Thank you.
Oh, that Italian brain rot.
Thank you. Can you see who you give me?
>> stuff. I give you brain
>> for that for that wooden guy.
The You don't have the wooden guy? No. I
like the brain. The brain is Oh, you
don't get the brain. It's got a I see.
No, I think I'd rather have the shark.
Open it up.
You're so excited, you're almost losing
it. Oh. Oh.
Yes. Yep. Yes.
>> is.
I always get what I want with these
things. That's pretty good.
>> last time and now I got the wooden brick
guy.
>> What about the banana? You have the
banana there?
>> No, he's nothing compared to the wooden
brick.
Yes.
>> I kind of like the ogre. The ogre's a
good one.
I don't even know his name. I know this
one's name.
Very good.
Made in Ireland, of all places. I doubt
it.
Can you tell me the most confidential
secret you learned while working at the
CIA you're not allowed to tell anybody?
Uh you know, people ask me on Cameo all
the time to tell them the deepest,
darkest secret. I can't.
Prison was not as hard as I thought it
would be, but it's not someplace I want
to go back.
>> So, you would go to jail again if you
did something like that?
>> sir. Okay, so maybe you tell me one and
then you can try to get out of it again
by telling a funny story afterwards.
I could I could, but I won't. Why? I
could tell you lots of funny stories.
I could tell you about this guy I was
sitting next to when we were writing
papers for the president. I was working
on an Iraq political paper, he was
working on an Iraq military paper and
I'm typing away, he's sitting next to
me, he's typing away and then he says,
"John." I turn, I look, and he goes, "I
think I'm having a heart attack." And he
falls off his chair.
I start to panic, I call 911, I run and
tell my boss, "Jeff's having a heart
attack." The paramedics come, they pick
him up, they put him on a gurney, they
strap him down to the gurney so he
doesn't have like a seizure and fall
off, and then he blows this ridiculous
fart.
Isn't that an indication of death? It
was an indication that it was just a
fart. And then he got off the gurney and
started typing the paper again. There
were like 20 people standing around.
>> have had less competition?
Nah, cuz we were like apples and
oranges. I didn't I I wasn't a friend of
the guy or anything, but I'm not going
to begrudge him life.
No, no, not begrudge him life, but you
wanted to wipe out the competition. No,
I Well,
yeah, I guess we were competing.
How would you feel if you didn't have
breakfast this morning?
Yeah, I didn't have breakfast, but I did
feel like I got ripped off on the size
of my coffee. But how would you feel if
you didn't? I did have a
large mocha that was like 12 oz. I said,
"Buddy, I ordered a large mocha." The
guy's like, "That is the large." I said,
"What planet do you live on?"
Okay, I think you're about to failing
the test.
>> Uh-oh.
Cuz you're answering with a real a real
answer, I think.
I think you failed it, but it's okay. I
I was just testing if you knew how to do
a hypothetical and you didn't.
>> Uh, sorry.
Well, see, but my reputation is as a
truth-teller. So, I got to tell you the
truth. Well, I think you're telling me
facts maybe. I guess it would be the
truth, but I think you're giving your
own take on it that I disagree with
about torturing people.
Okay, that that's cool. That's cool.
That's cool. You know, I I worked with
torture torturers, and most of them
were, you know, normally when they're
not torturing people, they're decent
guys. Our kids played together, our
wives were friends. Your kids and the
guy who was getting tortured's kids? No,
unfortunately, no.
>> Did he torture his kids, too?
Well, that's kind of a hypothetical, but
uh
not in my experience, I'll say it that
way. Well, really it actually isn't a
hypothetical at all.
Well, you know, there were rumors that
the CIA
>> didn't, yeah. Well, there were rumors
that the CIA tortured the kids of Khalid
Sheikh Mohammed.
That would be pretty cool, too, because
it's like who really in America get to
torture kids?
It's like a one-of-one experience maybe.
I would get in on that.
>> That's That's not a world I'd want to
live in. But you live in it, it seems
like. I hope not. Are you going to kill
yourself? Not myself.
>> So it seems like you want to live in
this world. Yeah, I'd like to
>> that trick there, that mind game?
>> you that was very that was very clever.
That was very clever, yes. Um I might
kill somebody else, but not myself. Is
that a threat of violence?
To the president? Uh no no no no no no
absolutely not. That's what it sounded
like. It's very you threatened to kill
the president.
>> no no no no not at all. No. That's very
illegal. You know, I was at that uh
dinner. Which one? With Kanye and Nick
Fuentes and Trump?
>> No, the White House Correspondents
Dinner. And I'm eating a salad.
>> one. Nick Fuentes wasn't there. Him and
Kanye and Trump.
Kanye? I didn't see Kanye at that
dinner.
Oh, so maybe this was a different one, I
guess. Go ahead, sorry.
I'm eating a salad and I said to my my
date,
"That can't possibly have been a
gunshot, right?"
And she's like, "No. No." And then we
just kept eating. And then everybody
started diving below the tables. Oh, the
one from a couple weeks ago. Yeah.
Yeah yeah, that wasn't the one. I'm
talking about the one in Mar-a-Lago,
like Uh the famous one where Kanye and
Nick Fuentes went. No. I went to I went
to Mar-a-Lago one time. I will admit to
you, it was the best egg salad I've ever
had in my life. But that was pretty much
the extent of it.
How would you sum up your experience
working for the Mossad?
My experience with the Mossad has been
that they probably wish they were
working for me. I mean the CIA, sorry.
>> Yes.
Uh One one in the same.
Pretty much.
How would you sum up that experience? Uh
you know, it was great until I realized
what the heck was actually going on.
But I did enjoy the travel. I went to 72
countries with the CIA. Which was the
worst one? Which had the worst most
despicable ugly people?
See, I'm going to get death threats for
answering you truthfully. Probably if
you answered correctly, these people
won't even have a phone to look at. I
hated India.
I just hated it. If you want to take a
[__] unfortunately they have phones. You
you want to take a [__] you're walking
down the street and people just pull
down their pants and take a [__] right
there on the street and then pull up
their pants and walk away. You saw that
happen? Every day. Every single day.
I've been in poorer countries
that they didn't do that. And I would I
say that that's a thing and then people
call me a racist. No, it's a thing. And
I am using it to racially insult Indian
Americans who don't do that sort of
thing but their their family does.
And it's in their blood to do it. I'll
tell you another thing I saw in India
that I hated. Is the people their color?
Standing No, standing right outside the
nice hotels where all these these dudes
wearing dresses and saris.
>> say nice hotel in India? Yeah, yeah,
like the Marriott and the Westin.
They're all these dudes wearing dresses
and I said to one of my Indian friends I
said, "What's with all these dudes
wearing saris and dresses?" And he said,
"Oh, yeah, they're they're criminals.
What they do is they come on weekends
and they disrupt people's weddings.
They'll go in and like smash the wedding
cake and throw chairs around and then
you have to pay them to leave. That's
how they make their living."
What a low level of like extortion type
thing. It's like the dumbest thing I've
ever heard.
Then why are they wearing dresses? I
didn't really get that part. I don't
know. It's just part of the stick, I
guess. So maybe they actually have some
sort of artistic sense in it.
I suppose you could look at it that way.
They're not just stupid gangsters.
Right.
You could look at it artistically.
Why did you stop that man from burning
himself alive? He may have been cold and
it would have heated everyone up.
No, when I got there he was just a black
spot on the ground. Are we talking about
the same thing? The guy was pouring the
oil on himself he was about to light
himself on fire.
No.
I saw you in the video You're in the
background.
>> Oh, that guy.
>> Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah. I did stop him
from setting himself on fire.
>> Why? Because we were all standing there
agreeing with each other.
It was this This was in front of the
Justice Department a couple of years
ago. It was It was a protest in support
of Julian Assange and WikiLeaks. And
this [__] guy
goes right up to the podium where we're
speaking, and he takes all of his
clothes off, so he's butt naked, and
then he squirts lighter fluid all over
himself, and he pulls out a lighter out
of his pants pocket that he had on the
ground. And a buddy of mine and I
>> Maybe he was trying to let all the
wildling tribes know that it's time to
attack the wall.
Maybe. Maybe the poor guy was just
having a mental breakdown.
Maybe Maybe he was cold also. It could
have been. So you're
>> Although it was a pretty comfortable day
that day.
I remember. It was a It was a warm day
in October. Yeah.
Yeah.
In fact, there was a woman there who was
an attorney, and she ran up to the cops
when the cops arrested him, and she
said, "I'm an attorney. He's clearly
mentally ill. Don't hurt him." Oh,
really?
>> Yeah. And instead of taking him to the
jail, they took him to the hospital,
which was kind of nice.
>> stopped him or the mental hospital?
Mental hospital. But he didn't even do
anything wrong. No, that's why they
didn't take him to jail. He didn't do
anything wrong.
>> No, why would they take him to the
mental hospital? He's clearly stable.
Yeah. Yeah, maybe for today's
Washington.
Would you put a rooster in your room to
wake you up when it's time? No, cuz the
roosters don't stop from like 3:00 in
the morning. I live next door to this
rooster in in Athens. I I wanted to go
out and kill it, and the only reason I
didn't is cuz my wife said she would
leave me if I did.
>> killed the rooster? Yeah. So what did
you do? You killed it? No, I just
>> still with your wife?
>> suffered. No. So then you So then Yeah,
I kind of chose the rooster over over
her.
Yeah, I mean, you should have just
expedited it then and killed rooster
then you wouldn't have had to go through
whatever divorce you did. I probably
still would have had to go through
>> Why didn't you just kill your wife? I
believe me it Didn't you have like
immunity or something?
That is a That is an issue that yeah,
could have been debated.
Right?
See, I come up with all these great
ideas that nobody ever takes advantage
of. Although you may have been
discontinued from the CIA
you would have come up with such a
genius idea. You would have killed your
wife and you wouldn't have had to go to
jail. Plus a rooster. Plus the rooster.
Yeah.
Do you CIA [__] be walking
around with the strap?
All the time. Why not?
You got to protect yourself. The next
guy's not going to protect you. What if
a [__] guy got flies in his ear? And
well he's going to have to deal with the
nine I had in a tearaway fanny pack on
my waist and the 38 on my ankle. And
just in case things turn to [__] I had
a buck knife in my back pocket. You one
of those Jewish [__] with a hat?
I didn't run into them overseas. I only
see them in New York. I want a [__]
guy to [__] be the lawyers and [__]
[__] guy you never get a hold of
them. They're always [__] They're
They're in the buildings and they don't
even be doing nothing. You don't even
know how to stop them.
Seriously.
Crazy [__]
Hey guys, sorry for the interruption. I
have to let you know that today's
episode is sponsored by Chubbies. If
you're sick of your usual shorts or
swimwear, then Chubbies is probably
perfect for you. Chubbies is also
celebrating its 15th anniversary. And to
celebrate, they're bringing back their
original shorts. I've personally been
wearing Chubbies a ton recently and I
can tell you from my own personal
experience that it's been great. The
shorts on the first wear feel like I've
already been wearing them for ages and
they fit great. That's partly also
because of the four-way stretch fabric
that they use. One of the best things
about Chubbies is the quality of the
shorts and especially the trunks.
They're extremely soft, extremely
flexible, and they're also extremely
quick drying as well. For a limited
time, Chubbies is offering listeners of
the show 20% off with my code Matan, m a
t a n at chubbieshorts.com.
That's code Matan, m a t a n to get 20%
off for a limited time at
chubbieshorts.com.
c h u b b i e s s h o r t s .com. Thank
you to Chubbies for sponsoring today's
episode, and if you buy something there,
let them know I sent you as it will help
the show.
You want to maybe switch chairs? Yeah.
>> So you can be closer to the mic. Okay.
Then hold that up for the rest of the
show. Okay.
Were you considered a snitch in prison?
No, thank God. No? I got a story there.
Okay.
The New York Times, the Sunday before I
went to prison. I went to prison on a
Thursday. New York Times front page
saying, he's going to this prison in
Pennsylvania. There was a guy there, an
Italian guy,
who became my best friend.
>> Yeah. And he
he took it upon himself to go to every
single one of the Italians and tell
them, "Listen, there's a CIA guy coming
on Thursday. He's not an FBI. FBI is
rats and snitches. CIA protected us from
the Muslims," he said. Okay.
And he said
>> You actually protected the Muslims.
Well, the Muslims thought I protected
the Muslims. The Nation of Islam guys.
The Nation of
The Nation of Islam guys.
What are you laughing at?
>> I I was thinking of these Nation of
Islam guys. Big ripped guys. One of them
came into my room the first day there,
and he handed me a newspaper that had a
>> you to read it for him? Well, the poor
guy, no, he had read it. But he said
>> read? Reverend he could.
>> Wow. Quite quite well. The He said,
"Reverend Farrakhan called me
the hero of the Muslim people. And so I
wasn't going to have any trouble with
them. So, I didn't. They were good. I
mean, they said that they I I put my
hand out to shake his hand and he says,
"I don't shake hands with the white
devil."
But, that I said, "That's cool."
>> to what? An Israelite?
Uh I don't know what he was.
>> Why are there more Israelites in the
CIA? Is it because they're already
There are more Mormons in the CIA cuz
they speak funky languages.
Oh.
Oh, [__]
Oh, it's not good. This is not good.
But, I think you're doing it on his
nose.
It's got to go It's got to go down his
throat. Okay. His mouth is right here.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, it's not See what I mean? It's not
good. Water, I think is the problem.
It's not good.
I I wondered what the hell you were
doing.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> You didn't do anything wrong. I'm just
torturing him because That Well, that's
the kind of the the idea.
You just take random people and do it to
them.
>> [snorts]
>> Yeah. See, it's not good. We can get
more going later. Yeah, you need like
gallon jugs. You know, actually, you
should try. I'm going to get
>> Uh yeah, thanks. You can bring your
back.
We we waterboarded each other in pract-
in the in training, practice. It was not
uh not pleasant.
Yeah. See,
he He got it all wrong, though. He's got
to be on a He's got to be on a on a
doing it wrong and he's got to be on a
board. That's why they call it the water
board.
And his feet have to be higher than his
head. And this towel is too thick. It
holds too much liquid.
You need like a like a pillow case.
Or a or
burlap.
Is this better? Yeah, that works.
But he's got to be laying almost flat.
Okay, we can do that as well.
Hold on to that for now.
>> Okay.
Lay flat.
I'm going to waterboard you if you don't
lay flat. Well, I'm going to waterboard
you anyways, but
So, not trying it out, John?
>> Okay, here you go.
Where's his mouth? There's his mouth.
>> [snorts]
>> See, that's why you need the gallon jug.
To keep going when they start coughing.
>> going to do anything. You're right. Get
out of here, now.
Get out of here, now.
You didn't tie him up tight enough.
What a waste of time.
I didn't even learn anything.
>> No, see, that's kind of the conclusion.
It's a waste of time.
He's good. He needs to
convulse first.
Maybe I can give him a concussion as
well.
We did that a lot. So, what's the next
best thing I should use on him?
Well, there are two next best things.
Okay. The first one is the cold cell.
You strip him naked, you chain him to an
eye bolt in the ceiling, you you chill
the cell to 50° F, and every hour you
throw a bucket of ice water on him.
The second thing is
>> have access to that though. Right. I
need something I can do like
waterboarding, it's simple. Sleep
deprivation. That takes a lot a lot
longer.
But I can do that. You need to go, you
know, 8 9 days without sleep. Then he
goes into organ failure. I mean, you
might as well just kill the guy at that
point.
Yeah, I mean, that's kind of the end
result half the time. Yeah, but that's
he's a terrorist, isn't he?
I don't know. I haven't met him.
Just look at his face.
He looks more like a crazy person than a
terrorist. He's the same one in the
same. Uh, these homeless people.
Jesus Christ.
Uh, why didn't the CIA ever consider
playing Soulja Boy to torture people?
You know, they did that all through the
Vietnam War. Oh, really? Oh my god, yes.
I don't think Soulja Boy was around
during the Vietnam War.
Was he? Oh, I thought you meant
colloquially soldier boy. I don't know.
I don't know what
>> No, no, Soulja Boy.
>> Yeah, oh, Soulja Boy.
>> Yeah, yeah, Soulja Boy. Yeah. Like kind
of like how I was talking a minute ago.
Yeah, Soulja Boy. Yeah, they could get
like
>> be confused with Soulja Boy. Uh, who's
that? He's Nigerian.
Isn't that also Soulja Boy? Oh, is he
Nigerian, too? You can't I mean
>> know. What do I know? I'm too old for
this kind of thing.
That's not something you guys ever
tried. I feel like it would be more
effective than all of the other ones.
>> No, what what what they did was they
played the Bee Gees on loop.
Or the SpongeBob SquarePants theme song.
So, they actually did something similar
to this. Yeah. But why SpongeBob? I love
that song.
>> I do, too.
But after you hear it 10,000 times, you
start to
>> you will know all the lyrics. Yeah.
So, actually
>> it's a good song, if it's like Bohemian
Rhapsody or something, okay, I could
sing that 10,000 times. Yeah, so I don't
get the why this is torture. Yeah. I
would much rather waterboard some guy.
Why does the man on the bus always ask
for three different coins, one metal,
one purple, and one green? He says, "If
I bring him the metal one, the purple
one doesn't come because the green one
absorbed it." He tells me the earth is
made of metal, purple, and green coins.
Is he right? And should I give him the
metal, purple, and green coins? That
sounds like about half the emails that I
get every day. Yeah, but this one's
real, unlike all those other ones.
>> Yeah, that one I don't know. But I
wouldn't be surprised if that was
communicated to you through a chip in
your brain or a filling in your tooth.
Is that something somebody's told you
before? Every single day.
I think maybe
this is some I'm MK Ultra stuff.
Stranger things have happened. And I
would like to get behind that. Is that
something they're still doing?
That's
the toughest question that you've asked
me so far. Oh, really?
>> They would say no.
I would say it's impossible to know.
But you might actually know the answer.
No, I wish I did. I'd blurt it out. So,
it seems like the answer from you is
yes. I mean
I mean, if I knew, I'd say yes, and I
would dare them to do something about
it. Why? Because then they'd have to
admit that it was true. Oh, really? So,
you wouldn't do another whistle-blow on
that level. I would. So, why don't you
tell me one of those secrets like I
asked from earlier? Because that stuff
is like sources and methods and, you
know, stuff that we need to keep secret
to try to keep the country safe and But
if you say something that can help not
keep the country safe, then maybe
and it's a big if, but it's a good one
if it can lead to the destruction of
Israel.
Yeah, it's it's not not for me.
You don't want to be responsible for
that? I do not.
Nah.
You're missing out. Yeah, maybe, but
that's not for me.
Is it true that you have to be at least
51% Jewish to be in the CIA?
I had not heard that.
Are you 51% Jewish?
>> I'm not. I'm like 2% Jewish according to
23 and me. It's always a trick though.
It's like are you Jewish? Just a little
bit. And it's always more than they say.
>> I will tell you a true story.
My mother's maiden name was
Chrisopoulos.
When a Greek name ends in opolis, that
just means you're from the Peloponnesian
Peninsula. But the first part of the
name
Chriso, it means gold. And I said to my
mom one time, your name doesn't make any
sense to me. And she said, what do you
mean?
And I said, gold.
I said, gold. It
she says,
probably somebody in our family was a
was a jeweler. And I said, no, we were
farmers for 2,000 years. I think it's
more probably like Goldman or Goldberg
or Goldstein.
>> Goldberg. Yeah. So I
>> Yeah, I don't even know. Oh, he had a
great spear. And so I did a 23 and me
and it said, yes, Jewish on my mother's
father's side.
From Lithuania, no less.
You see what I'm saying? It's always
It's like you your mother's maiden name
is Goldberg. You see what I mean?
That's just life.
>> But let's assume that's not true or if
it was you can't tell me. It's one of
those secrets.
What how many Jews did you see in the
CIA? A lot of them?
I never really paid attention to tell
you the truth. It's right out in the
open with them sometimes.
I don't know.
>> You could look at me and know that I'm
not Jewish. You know what I mean?
I don't actually. No?
I feel pretty insulted right now. Sorry,
didn't mean to rain on on the parade.
In what year
did you end up leaving the CIA?
>> 2004. So you were in the CIA during
9/11?
>> Oh yeah. You have anything you can tell
us about that?
Probably a lot I can tell you about
that. Anything like uh new? Any new
info? No, it's pretty much all out
there. Really? Pretty much. Do you
believe it was an inside job? No. No? I
don't. It was a terrorist attack from
Al-Qaeda? Yes. No Jewish? No, but
>> to Andrew Bustamante, the leader of the
CIA, former leader.
>> Oh yes.
>> And he told me that it was the Jewish.
>> Yeah. Uh no, I think that the Israelis
knew it was coming and didn't warn us
because they knew that if we were
attacked, we would end up doing what
they wanted and just go around the world
kill Muslims, which is exactly what
happened.
When we captured Abu Zubaydah, we also
captured his diary. And in his diary, he
had the personal cell phone numbers of
three Saudi princes. So we went to the
Saudis very angrily and said, "You
better do something about this." And the
next thing you know, one prince dies in
a one-car accident on the Riyadh to
Jeddah highway. One prince
>> Yeah, well one one prince goes in for
stomach surgery and dies on the
operating table. And one prince goes
into the desert to go camping and dies
of thirst.
That makes sense. I mean, he's in the
desert. Yeah, but he's he camps in the
desert all the time. You'd think he
would take a bottle of water. Maybe he
ran out. He was trying to waterboard
somebody. He wasted all of it. Drink
your own piss then and save yourself.
Get in the car.
>> Does that work? Drive to a 7-Eleven.
>> it was like drinking salt water.
>> I don't know. I've never tried it. It's
like drinking ammonia, it seems like to
me.
Hey guys, sorry for the interruption. I
have to let you know that today's
episode is sponsored by PrizePicks. The
NBA regular season is over and the
playoffs are here. So there's no better
time to cash in than now. PrizePicks is
now also a preferred partner of the NBA
and it's available in all 50 states
including California, Texas, Georgia,
and all of the other ones. On Prize
Picks you get to choose how you play. If
you want flexibility, then you can
choose to do a flex play, meaning that
you can get paid out even if one of your
picks misses. And if you want the
biggest payout, then you can go for the
power play. My buddy Mike has been using
Prize Picks a lot recently and he's been
loving it. He especially likes one of
their new features which is the early
payout, meaning that if your player gets
off to a hot start, you can cash out if
your pick hits before the game even
ends. Download the Prize Picks app today
and use my code Matan, m a t a n, to get
$50 for free in lineups after playing
just your first $5 lineup. That's my
code Matan, m a t a n, to get $50 for
free in lineups after playing just your
first $5 lineup on the Prize Picks app.
Thank you to Prize Picks for sponsoring
today's episode. Prize Picks, a
preferred partner of the NBA. Trump
recently said, "I believe I'm going to
hell and the only way for me to get into
heaven is by destroying 13 more
elementary schools in Iran."
Is he correct?
Uh no.
Why?
Uh
Yeah, we should we shouldn't be we
shouldn't be in the business of
attacking elementary schools anywhere. I
agree with that, but he needs to do it
to go to heaven.
No, I think he needs to respect
international human rights to go to
heaven. Remember he's supposed to be the
peace president. He's going to win the
Nobel Peace Prize. He's making peace all
over the world, so
Yeah, he wanted he forced that girl into
giving it to him. Did you see that?
Yeah.
So he kind of won it because he didn't
kill her or anything. He kind of got it
through a peaceful method.
>> just took it. Yeah. She offered it up.
She gave it to him. What a nice lady.
And uh you've met him? Yeah, I've met
him. How was that experience?
>> He
Honestly, he was lovely. You want him to
give you your pension back. I hope he
does. I'm waiting.
Let's see.
>> do you not get from that? Uh all
together it was $700,000.
Will you get all of it back? I would get
all of it back. Yeah.
>> In a in retro, whatever it's called.
Yeah. Retroactively.
>> Retroactively. And then how much do you
get a year? What is it like 50
>> Oh, it's not it's not a ton. Yeah, it's
just under $50,000.
>> Is that a That's less than you made when
you worked there, right?
>> Oh, yeah, way less. Yeah.
>> How much did you make? What's the pay? I
think when I left I was making not a
ton. I was making maybe 110, 112. But in
in 2004 that was good money.
It seems like a stressful job for 100
grand a year. Yeah, but you don't do it
for the money. You do it cuz you're a
patriot. Or to torture people. There are
unfortunately some people who do it for
that reason, yes. You say unfortunately,
I say that it's the they're destroying
terrorism. No, they're not.
>> Has there been any more terrorism since
then?
>> Oh, lots. Yes.
Lots. I disagree with that. Okay. Tell
ISIS.
No, they've been defeated. Oh, have
they? Yes.
>> I missed that. They've all been
defeated.
By the great white hope. Yes.
Do you like white boys in the
No, I've never never given it a try.
>> That's not my question. That's from Bird
B U R T
Oh, okay. That's what his name stands
for. It's a weird question, but I had to
ask.
What?
Oh, I got Some gay thing reference. I
don't know. It's disgusting, really.
Yeah, yeah, it's not for me.
No, you don't? No.
Now, I can't really relate to him, but I
guess I'll try to continue the this
conversation or this questionnaire
on his behalf. I guess the follow up
would be why.
Uh yeah, it's just it doesn't do do
anything for me. Could you use MK Ultra
to turn somebody into a gay?
I mean, if MK Ultra had worked out the
way they wanted to it to work out, you
can turn them into anything. You can
turn them into an assassin. That was the
idea.
What about
What about a gay? Probably.
And you could hypothetically
make somebody not gay anymore?
Geez, I have no idea.
If that's true, I feel like
maybe we need to get behind and start a
GoFundMe or something. Well, I mean, if
we already have hypnosis, isn't that the
same thing? You hypnotize someone so
they stop they stop smoking. You
hypnotize someone so they remember
something
really important.
>> Yeah, no, I've seen it work.
>> You've seen it work?
>> I worked with a hypnotist while I was on
an operation.
Maybe we're talking about different
levels of one, but I've
>> Maybe. I've seen some and they seem to
be liars.
Oh, I think most of them are probably
frauds. But one that I worked with, it
was the real deal.
See, but when they when it works, it's
only for a limited period, though.
>> Yes. Yes. With MK Ultra, you could
hypothetically get somebody forever.
Yeah, but then you're going to have them
jump off the roof of a hotel or hang
themselves from a tree and all kinds of
crazy things that happens.
>> I don't know, man. It didn't work out in
practice.
Why not? I don't know. It just didn't
work. Maybe it did actually. That's why
Oh. Nah, we started in 1952, ended in
1975 and had nothing legit to show for
it.
Yeah, there's actually way more gay
people nowadays than before, so
There's way more autistic people now
than there were before, too.
So it really must have failed.
Something's going
>> Whole operation like was a big spit in
our face.
Something
something's going on.
Can you tell me about that? Some
I don't know about it. That was way
before my time.
You weren't born then? You weren't in
the CIA in the 50s?
>> in the CIA. No, no, I was I was born in
1964. So, I missed it. So, if you were
like 9 years old though, you could have
been around in there.
I guess I could have been in those
circles if I was 9 years old.
>> did it to you as a kid. Well, have you
heard the the joke that we're all
trained to tell?
No. Yeah, they train us to tell this one
joke.
This joke is I'm driving around McLean,
Virginia by the CIA and I see a sign.
It's on the
it's on a telephone pole. It says,
"Talking dog and for sale." It has an
address. So, I go over to the address
cuz I wasn't in a hurry. And I knock on
the door and I said to the guy, "You got
a talking dog for sale?" The guy says,
"Yeah." I said, "Can I see it?" He says,
"It's around the back." So, I go around
the back and there's a dog sitting
there. It's a mutt.
And I said, "Hello." And the dog looks
at me. You know how dogs do their head
like that?
And he goes, "Hello." I said, "Oh my
god, you do talk." And he said, "Yeah,
that's how I got a job at the CIA." I
said, "I I work at the CIA." He said,
"Yeah, I was in counter-terrorism." I
said, "I'm in counter-terrorism." "What
did you do in counter-terrorism?" He
said, "Well, because I talk, they sent
me on to Bin Laden's compound and I
listened to what Bin Laden was saying
and I come out and I tell them. And that
went so well, I went I went to Kim
Jong-un and I listened to what he was
saying and I came out and told them. And
then finally, they sent me to the
Kremlin. I listened to what Putin's
saying and I came back and I told them."
I said, "That's incredible. You're an
American hero." I said, "I'm going to
buy you." So, I said to the guy, "How
much you want for this dog?" He goes,
"20 bucks." I said, "Why so cheap?"
He said, "That damn dog's a liar. He
didn't do any of that stuff."
What's the joke? I don't get it.
See, my sister reacted the same way.
I always thought it was
[__] hilarious. If I
>> a talking dog, I'd I'd [__] get ready
to battle.
But he's just laying there. He's not
threatening you in any way. He's
threatening me by being a dog that's
talking to me. Well, he's a liar.
>> I'm either crazy and I need to kill this
dog because I'm crazy.
>> to rat you out on something? Well, I
mean if what he's saying is true, then
yes.
Listen to what the dog just told you.
But the guy said the dog made it all up.
It was just all made up. He said that's
why it was only $20.
But this guy is interacting with you as
if the dog was actually talking? Yeah,
the dog's a
>> a liar dog? He's a liar.
But the dog is talking. Yeah, he's just
lying.
>> Then the dog needs to be eliminated.
I mean, this is beyond even a talking
dog. This is a sophisticated conscious
dog that's lying to you so you buy him.
Yes.
You sure it's not just like a [__] in
a little
Could have been a [__] Wait a minute.
I think we're not supposed to say [__]
anymore.
I mean, who are you going to offend,
midgets? What are they going to do to
you?
Yeah.
They're going to bite your leg?
Truly like a dog.
>> it.
I don't even think we have [__]
throwing contests in bars anymore.
I I wish there were still like those
clowns who used to try to ride lions,
which was really just dogs that they
would put big ears on. Right. Now these
guys, it's always you have to [__]
pay them $500 an hour to debate a clown
and a Domino's employee and Stiney and
another clown. It's getting ridiculous.
You know what I'm talking about?
>> disagree.
$500 an hour for a [__]
That's ridiculous.
>> Of course, you don't want to begrudge
the [__] a living. The guy's got to
make a living. And you know He needs
half of a normal living.
>> Whatever the whatever the market will
bear, that's the price.
That's the one thing that I don't agree
with capitalism on.
Huh.
Think about that.
I think I do agree with capitalism on
that. That there can be midgets with a
lot of money? Sure, why not? Makes us
look like an underdeveloped [__]
country.
I'm not even sure the last time I saw a
Why did the CIA create a myth?
Is it to distract everybody by making
them laugh too much? That could be it.
Yeah. It could be
so that they can sneak into places and
not be noticed.
You know what I noticed though?
They're all very stupid. No.
>> Yes, they are. I worked for a myth. It
is
>> Oh god.
>> first office director at the CIA. She
was brilliant. in the CIA.
>> actual myth.
And she was brilliant.
I thought we were the most I thought we
were the best country. We are you know
we are the best country. I'm not even
going to Russia and telling them that
there's a myth in the in their whatever.
I bet there is.
They'd probably rip your neck off if you
insinuated it.
>> There's got to be one. There's got to
be. No.
Yeah, now I think I'm against
capitalism.
I think my I've shifted.
No, I'm
I'm just now getting my first taste of
capitalism. I'm liking it pretty pretty
well. Just recently you've been making a
lot more money? Finally. What about the
money you were paid by the Russian state
media? Yes, they don't pay very much.
No? Did you have to tell them any of the
CIA secrets or you just had to
>> Nope, they never asked. They said They
said, "Here's a microphone. We give you
a radio show. Knock yourself out." And
what did you talk about usually on the
show? Whatever happened to be in the
news that day. Oh, really? Mhm. Did you
have to take Russian positions on it?
>> Nope. Were you working for them when the
Ukraine war started? Uh yes. And what's
your position on that?
>> The very first thing I said on my radio
show that day was, "I unreservedly
condemn the Russian invasion of Ukraine
and I call on Russian troops to withdraw
immediately."
And then you were fired.
>> Nope.
It was part of my contract that I could
say anything I wanted and criticize
anybody I wanted. What about Log Neck? I
don't know who that is. He's my next
guest in 5 minutes.
>> Oh.
Are you allowed to criticize him? Of
course.
I don't I criticize everybody cuz I got
nothing to lose. So, can you criticize
him?
Why not?
Go ahead. Where is he?
He's a he's a little bit late. He's
supposed to be here 5 minutes ago. He's
5 minutes away though. Okay.
So, give him some critis- criticism. But
I don't know anything about him. I can't
even mock his physical appearance. I'll
show you a photo of him and you will.
Oh, yeah. He's that that's one ugly
[__] guy. Yeah. See what I said?
>> Yeah, yeah. That's not Yeah. He's here
in 5 minutes by the way.
>> money with that neck? I doubt it. I
doubt it too.
>> Does he look like he has a lot of money?
No.
Although his lick here tattoo probably
cost what? 150 bucks?
I feel like that's probably like a
sponsorship he did. Ah, I didn't even
think of that. It probably is.
>> him with that tattoo. Yeah.
Gross.